make them bad health-wise I think I'm
doing okay
more or less um but I don't I don't know
what to do and being okay with that like
if I knew what if it was within my power
in any way I would do it but it's not
and I get that it's not supposed to be
within my power I'm not supposed to be
the one to do the work because what if I
was what if someone just gave me a
million dollars and said make the first
thing I would know what to do that I'd
probably spend it too fast and it'd be
gone and then but that's the beauty of
what I want to create is that we need to
have thresholds met before we move
forward which is why I like the idea of
having a million members paying $10 a
month and that like deferred rush holds
met before we move forward which is why
I like the idea of having a million
members paying $10 a month and that the
like different phases and how they're a
little bit confusing so it's like a
first we're only gonna pay $10 per
project and then after once we unlock
simultaneous project so we're gonna pay
$10 per month because the truth is it'd
be great to have $10 per month right off
the bat that's 120 mil at art much more
does it again one point five seven ten
million dollars a month 120 million
dollars a year to fix the world and the
world needs fixing and that's why I feel
like crap it's just all the people
migrating around the world due to war
and climate change and climate changing
people starving the property that exists
even in our country in the United States
you feeling like I have something to
offer to solve that which is just like
we need to solve it we need the system
in place to be able to collaborate
together to be able to understand
complex problems not everyone has to
understand every calm
every piece of every complex problem the
point is we can't do that that's
impossible
but even that maybe it's not like
climate change is complex science is bad
at understanding complex stuff but the
more what we do have access to is
trustworthy and available to everyone
some high school student can solve
something maybe him like when you give
people access to the information and
they don't have to have a PhD before
they're even like allowed at the table
of a conversation more people can be
happy that conversation like we just
need the tools in place we need to need
the tools we need to have organization
of the knowledge and that like and I
believe in this but what if I'm the only
what like I don't nothing all that I'm
already not the only one but I mean to
some degree that okay with putting my
time and energy into this and having to
go nowhere because I'm enjoying the
process and it's teaching me a lot about
myself I want a really real scale not
okay if they're not going anywhere
because I thought okay with it something
similar happening in the world and me
not being a part of it and hopefully if
it is truly something similar I'm old to
come on board with with them because
everyone's invited if it is truly
similar to what I'm doing like there's a
few things of inclusivity transparency
and democracy that I think everyone has
to hasta clockwise I mean the truth is a
lot of these ideas could be
million-dollar ideas that I could make
profit off of if I was able to create
them myself but I'm not able to create
them myself and the whole point is to
not have that inefficiency to not have
dozens of apps that dozens of dozens of
individual people own having one central
database that explains it and maybe
that's what I'll do if I can find my
pins I'm gonna explain so one of the
things that's bugs me is that we don't
have access to knowledge and for someone
who I have knowledge on a very high
esteem a whole dollars very high esteem
like I can see where I could like it's
like oh if I only knew
piece of knowledge I can helpful to
solve this and anyway that like I make
assumptions I make my own personal
viewpoints based on what I know to be
true what I think I know to be true
there's been times I'm sure everyone has
experienced this for something that you
that's just wrong like that doesn't
exist that's not true and you look it up
and they're right you're like oh that
was ok I can get that from I don't know
a lot of it's like it's an old wives
tale isn't like no this is like this is
the truth but being able to I'm sure
I've also given people faulty
information and then because it's come
from me and they trust my intelligence
it becomes somewhat ironclad and like
you don't even like we don't necessarily
even know where we get it from and then
I get it corrected but I don't remember
everyone else I told it wrong too and
get it redirected so here's to have data
that we can trust that six scible and
what that means is having one central
database that contains Oh data so that's
like data on corporations data on
science as well as our own personal data
this is like one big and it doesn't mean
there's only one central location you
can still have blockchain you can solve
the efficiency of having in and the
security of having it in different
locations but that there's one
fundamental place even if it's I'm going
in a different place is that when this
is updated it goes up and out updates
everything else so if we decide all of a
sudden it's like wait it turns out the
world is only sixty thousand years old
it would go through and at least take
where those things are like where does
the data come from and then where is it
used and that's the so it can come from
like input like we break down tasks and
say here's everything we want to know
right this is it has to go into there so
it's just like people and put it in that
entry can be a game they give you so you
take a picture of this you update gasps
you get points you gamify it
as well as all of the things that are
going out also go back in so this is
technology that look at that ear
listening to you it is making sense
right so if you create an app that uses
that data website that uses that data so
this is like every recipe every health
thing about every ingredient and you
create a food recipe and then your
people you this is a nuns of these are
what you're using these in is anything
right studies if it's that good of data
helps tech but all of them are also
feeding back in right if you do a study
to study feeds back in right it's back
in there so for every piece of data you
can see where it comes from and the
grading of it right because things
aren't black and white it's like okay
but like how many people died in World
War two in every different country right
there's different estimates there isn't
one concrete number so it's like okay
what are those estimates where do they
come from and why do we trust one versus
another and so we can say I mean if
there is somehow one that stands out
above everyone else that that's the one
that we all agree with but if you don't
agree with it you could tweak this so
that for you it's it's but you've got to
kind of be aware right like no actually
didn't exist World War two never
happened like um actually that's
ridiculous but that one central place
for data so when it's corrected it goes
updates everything but also so that it's
our data that we all can use like we get
to put our data in there to like our
medical information because we like and
that's kind of more of like a little
where I like your own personal data cuz
it doesn't necessarily mean it's part of
the big data maybe you only have access
to it until you choose to open it up but
it's still you're inputting it or your
game affiant because our medical
information combined gives us way more
information than just my personal
medical information but only voluntarily
and safe so that it's washed and you
don't know it's fine
you only know that there's like my
demographics right but there's like a 38
year old female whatever points you want
and those things if we're not
comfortable with anyone having access to
any points because I can get scary
it becomes the people the crowd is the
barrier so it's like hey I want to learn
this I want to do this study and there's
certain things that are open maybe
you've gots three points of data right
you can know age and gender and status
whatever the three things you want to
know but if you want to a fourth you
need it okay tour whatever it happens to
be right we can set the guidelines but
having why does daddy not excite other
people I don't understand you understand
what we can do have data like honestly
though if we had just our health data if
we had because we have we buy fitbit's
we pick to spend money so that a
corporation can have our data it's like
we can do that even though if we own the
Fitbit I believe we own the information
it's the least as far as like we can
upload our own it use our own data and
the your genome sequence either things
like 23andme
or actually getting your genome
sequenced which is like about dollars
and would give a ton of information as
to especially in a population right
having data so that it updates itself so
it's like okay well I don't know we
don't how to explain it but like if
there's ways it goes into the system and
so there can be plenty of ways right
there can be like nearly infinite number
of games that we create that get the
data but if every game was its own
unique thing that it's not having the
efficiency the efficiency comes from it
be in one database so that when you know
when you if something's not in here you
can put the call out to be like oh
actually for this app we're creating we
need to have product information right
so what does that look like and it goes
oh maybe it's the next step is pay but
each one having its own I don't even
know friend or I'm saying like this is a
piece of it like what we can do with
data and technology is infinite like
just from my mind I can only imagine
when like we have this the whole point
is I have things I could do with this
data especially when working out pretty
much only working with other people
other people have their own ideas of
what to do with it but as you create
like everyone has full access to it so
as you create you don't necessarily get
full access get to make something for
profit make it proprietary and then sell
it back to us
no but you get to use the data for
nonprofits you possibly even get to use
it for profit if it's transparent people
have located it but when you create data
it goes back up to the system right you
have your own recipe app for some reason
you've decided you're going to make and
have it be for a profit even though
probably the key one that will kick your
butt but if you're using the data that's
coming out you're also giving the data
back in you don't get to use our recipes
and then not give your recipes back
right it's a reprocessing your personal
one is not the same your personal
information you can if you're someone
who's comfortable not you're not
comfortable sharing your information
then you get to not share your
information you still get the benefit of
like the group information because it's
and honestly you're not going to get the
full benefit of the group information
unless you give your data not because
not for ethical reasons not because it's
decided by the crowd it's just how it is
right if you have access to everyone
else's Fitbit data and you haven't given
yours in you don't know what your heart
rate is right you don't know where you
fit on the normal curve you don't so
it's like it's not actually not helpful
and I see you also put yours in now if
you can see yours and nobody else can
then that is what what helps and what we
might not be able to do you might not be
able to access group information for
your benefit unless you're also giving
your information to the group but that's
something for us to decide Emma
chronically which one were more from on
okay we're but yeah that we have no I
don't like what this looks like it's
just like it doesn't look like this
right it's like okay well data forms
like okay there's this website that has
artifacts it's just clearly an artifact
and so have anything in there yet you
say okay well we want pictures of all of
the things and all of the museums around
the world it's a lot of information and
you
it's already in a game it's like any
game they can just take pictures and get
this stuff and you were on points it can
just go into that to question it but
then what was my point you earn data you
do as people are filtering it in it
might be a piece in the game I'm sorry
in the app itself it's like you can oh
we don't have your Museum hey you can
add the museum itself can add themselves
they can add their their items to it
tell us where it's from my point of this
was but just that then it's feeding back
into it right so like this can be a
pretty sight that looks very
professional like my picture here that
showcases history in a way that like
brings it to life for everyone but
positive things are inputted in here
it's added to here and as people maybe
there's a different one thing I can't
remember like maybe you're a category
category
cataloging like your grandparents attic
and that might there might be a helpful
piece so that you can input it and it's
like when they die hey we'd like this
Pete like this would like to have this
donate it or we'd like to buy it from
whatever it happens to be right there
can be different point I think this I
feel like this is dead or showcased in
like a dating site so this is now a
dating site and a set of a museum site
so people put their demographics or
profile their pictures and everything
else on the dating site it goes into you
a common database so that with you have
a niche something that's that's like
this is kind of a skin it's the skin so
it can be unique it can look different
it can be aesthetically pleasing to you
it can be nice it can be all of those
things but you still have the efficiency
of the data behind it so that you can
have you know an app for trans farmers
to find each other right that it's like
okay but what are the chances that that
you're ever gonna reach a threshold of
those people to have a viable dating
site next to zero but if you're coming
out of here actually no because you're
going to have people who if that is
their nation it's what they're really
looking for can find transformers and if
they are a transformer can find other
people
right here I mean it very much depends
what kind of trans you are my point is
just like the more nish you are possibly
the harder it is to find yourself your
people in the mainstream but you can
have the best of both worlds you can
have like the Meany niche dating sites
that also draw on the bigger data set so
that they're all but like as people join
your farmer dating site it's also going
back back into it right it's going back
and do it so that there's you know same
with recipes it's like you have your own
like peanut free I'll other G site for
peanut free people and as you correct
recipes that maybe used to be peanuts
now there are peanuts that's a bad one
gluten free recipe site then it also
goes back into the system right so it's
making it more efficient because it's
able to be organized in a way that when
data is truly changed and we're like oh
new evidence came out we can see
everywhere it ripples down and it's not
a blog written in 2015 that doesn't
really have any references that were all
referencing it didn't come from anywhere
and stopped going anywhere right I kind
of wrote there there's a bunch of things
that we think of as um truth that aren't
and they started in movies and it's just
like but it's the truth because it was a
movie so it became the truth it became
like folklore now it's just yeah I feel
a little better now that I've explained
data but not because I also get that
this is not very clear to people and I
actually don't even know how to percent
of us as possible but it's what I'm
because they do like when you see any
wet ingredients or carcinogens from
actual science and we're only allowing
in science that's a beer a beer and a
right any C or D science isn't getting
at Earth is it's very clearly showcasing
that it's C D and F science right so
yeah like you can use the data to create
new things and as you creative worth
people we're doing it together so we can
decide how much ownership we allow
people to have with
right if I the idea for a business
around property and how much profit are
you allowed to generate when you're
using a not-for-profit system if you
come up with with innovation because I
would like to defaults on not profit to
flip it from the uber competitors the
uber co-operators that are being propped
up in society like I would love for uber
co-operators to be the new one and if
there's any 1% cuz they truly do bring
everybody up because they're the
corporators that's what they want to do
uber competitive's their whole point is
to like the best be the best tell me I'm
the best you know it's just like rule in
the world whereas when the co-operators
it's like is everybody Damini okay so
every meets everyone okay okay I can say
no right so yes I'm going to end this
here 20 minutes and one day one day
they'll be people things that they'd get
what I'm trying to say and one day I'll
figure out how to say it properly so
it's succinct maybe maybe not cuz right
now I'm sitting with do a crowds look at
make it more succinctly which is not my
talent and we can have million members
basically overnight paying into a system
so that we can create they're paying for
hope and we're delivering hope and
they're part of the we so having a
system that allows that and getting to
that point again it's not utopia like
the Enochian future where like this is
in place and we're honoring our
individuality and we have all the
technology in place to live our best
lives because it's like our own personal
assistant health and response a trained
trainer what's called trainer
mmm-hmm fitness trainer you could have
the crowd design and talk with your
hosts and where there aren't enough
people that want to do that and I think
they're actually probably definitely are
um people like aesthetics people who
like decoration other people's houses
especially if you don't have to
physically go there I didn't do the
you're just giving you options like yeah
this would look good with this color
like your book you could like Pinterest
your own house right and be like we'd
like and then you get to pick from it
well like I'd like it like this but a
computer could generate those things
right it measures your Rawls and there
is everything that's there it says
wherever you like can even say hey all
this stuff's not in place if you look
drop my room it's very messy and it's
like hey this needs to go here can even
like of an algorithm and can bet a
better camera if it could you like 360
it takes pictures it's like alright put
your stuff away in this order game of
fly cleaning up your hover kid or clean
up your room for kids right it knows
what you have it knows what you got for
Christmas house you got for your
birthday and that's where the data set
comes in right like you were buying
things so it's like that it's in here
data for things like oh we know you have
all these toys we know your rooms this
big hey which surprised your room for
you put all these things back where they
go or gonna tell you where they are
tying you right and someone creates that
game because it's fun for their kid but
but everyone has access to it right as
if they want to give up you don't have
to give up there like if you're creating
something personal for your own use and
you're never gonna sell it you don't
need permission but if you're creating
something that you want to be able to
sell that's what are you probably
approaching for creating it and then
just giving it away or selling it it's
parent about it and that's more what it
will be it's not even necessarily if you
use this to create something and then I
live for 5000 markup guess what we're
gonna do we're just gonna mimic how you
did and sell it at cost so you have to
compete with people who are willing to
sell it at cost the only way to do that
is to be transparent and show that you
have more to give and like us taking it
over
right which is like okay cool that's
awesome you create that you keep it you
know what like of a game is two bucks
and someone put a bunch of time into
I'll give them two bucks for the game
especially when I know they're a decent
person and it's not I don't know
horrible person doing my two dollars -
okay today's live slash not so much
video you all know buddy twirl bye